The exploitation revelation of the year!
Bullets of Justice is a action, horror, comedy film directed by Valeri Milev.
During World War III, the American government initiates a secret project codenamed ‘Army
Bacon’ in order to create super soldiers by inbreeding humans with pigs.
25 years later the hybrid Muzzles have occupied the top of
the food chain, eating and farming humanity.
Ex-bounty hunter Rob Justice works for the last line of human resistance - a group of survivors hiding in a
nuclear bunker deep underground - and his mission is to search and destroy Muzzle Central.
Rob Justice, played by Timur Turisbekov.
Raksha, played by Doroteya Toleva.
Gravedigger, played by Danny Trejo.
Nina, played by Yana Marinova.
Liudmila, played by Neli Andonova.
General Askar, played by Askar Turisbekov.
Bullets of Justice is a film made by Valeri Milev and Timur Turisbekov.
Originally shot in 2017 as a pilot episode for a series, after a reconsideration of a concept it was eventually
extended into a full feature film premiering at London FrightFest Film Festival on the 23rd of August 2019.
The film explores themes of army, bounty hunter,
government, experiment, mutation.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.